https://www.cocklestorm.com/about-us/privacy-policy/

Cart
£0.00
You have no items in your shopping cart.
SEARCH
Search:
>
Privacy Policy | Cocklestorm Fencing Ltd | Manchester & Bury
About Cocklestorm
Cocklestorm Privacy Policy
This Privacy Policy explains how we use any personal information you provide to Cocklestorm when you use our services in our Stores, our Website or any other contact you have with us.
"Cocklestorm/We" means Cocklestorm Fencing Ltd (as the operator of the Stores and Website).
We respect your right to privacy and are committed to maintaining it. We only collect, store and process your personal information in accordance with the relevant laws and regulations.
Accessing, browsing or otherwise using our Website confirms that you have read and understood this Privacy Policy. Please ensure you read it carefully, particularly the section detailing your rights in relation to the personal information that we collect about you.
To help to navigate this policy it is split up into the following sections:
What Information We Collect About You+
The personal information collected from you is dependant upon the services you are using:
• Name and Title
• Home, Billing and Delivery Address
• Email Address
• Phone Number
• Purchase information
• Payment card information
• Account Password and Login details
• Your comments, product reviews and responses on surveys you complete
• Your images on CCTV
• Your car number plate if recorded to manage parking at our Stores
• IP Address
• Device information
• Website / Browsing History, including location data
• Cookie information (please see our Cookie Policy for details)
When Do We Collect Information About You+
We collect personal information when you:
• Purchase products or services through the Website (including the mobile site), over the phone, through our stores or through social media
• Create an Account
• Obtain a quote or fitting enquiry for materials or services
• Subscribe to our newsletters
• Submit reviews or choose to complete surveys we have sent you
• Enter our competitions, prize draws or promotions
• Use our customer services team or contact us for any reason, e.g. order queries, complaints, website issues, phone, email and postal correspondence
• Complete a form, such as for a transaction or employment purpose or for accident or incidents in stores or for other health and safety or security purposes
• Use our car parks and stores which usually have CCTV systems operated for the security of both customers and colleagues
• Browse the website - please see the section on cookies for more information
How We Use Your Personal Information+
We use your personal information in several different ways, depending upon the type of information you provide. You do not have to provide this personal information, but if you don't then you may not be able to purchase goods from us, we may not be able to provide certain services and you are unlikely to receive our optimal overall customer experience.
Below explains in detail, what we do, and why we do it:
Your name and contact details
• To perform our contract with you - To fulfil your order, i.e. taking payment, updating you regarding the status of your order and dispatching the order to you.
• To manage any issues during order fulfilment - We have to do this to perform our contract with you. We may also keep a record of this to adhere to our legal obligations.
• To register you for My Account - We have to do this to perform our contract with you. Where you have not yet purchased anything, we will ask you if you want to consent to email marketing through this registration.
• To verify your identity when you access your account online or to contact you to perform security checks - We have a legitimate interest in ensuring that you are who you say you are to ensure good and services are provided to the correct person.
• For the detection and prevention of fraud or any other crimes - We have a legitimate interest in protecting ourself from fraud.
• To monitor and improve the running of the website, including monitoring browsing activity and session replays - We have a legitimate interest in monitoring our website to improve the user experience.
• To send you marketing promotions, offers, competitions and events by email - We have a legitimate interest in selling our products.
• To send you service emails or communication required by law to update you about any amendments to our goods and/or services - We need to do this to adhere to our legal obligations.
Your Payment Details
• To fulfil your order, i.e. taking payment, updating you regarding the status of your order and dispatching the order to you - We must do this to perform our contract with you and our contracts with partners and suppliers who work with us to provide the service to you.
• To evaluate customer spend within our store and website - We have a legitimate interest in interpreting this information to improve customer/user experience.
Your Username & Password
• To prove your identity when you access your account - We have a legitimate interest in ensuring that you are who you say you are to make sure goods and services are provided to the correct person/address.
Your Image On CCTV
• To protect the safety and security of work colleagues and customers and the avoidance or detection of unlawful acts - We have a legitimate interest to protect ourself from crime, and to provide safe working surroundings for our staff.
How Long We Will Store Your Personal Information+
Cocklestorm will hold on to your personal information for as long as you have your account with us, or as long as is needed for us to be able to provide the relevant goods or services to you. Our general length of time to keep customer's information is for 7 years.
In some circumstances, i.e. to adhere our legal obligations, resolve disputes, prevent fraud or enforce our terms and conditions, we may hold on to your personal information after we’ve finished providing services to you, or for longer than our policy sets out.
Your Rights For Your Personal Information+
As the information we hold about your is your personal information, you have many rights on it and how it is used. Below outlines the rights which are available to you and how to make use of those rights.
Your rights include (but are not limited to):
• To be informed about what we do with your information
• To access your information.
• To correct your information
• To delete your information (unless we have a legitimate reason to keep hold of it).
This Privacy Policy will keep you informed about how we will use your personal information. You are able to request access to the personal information we hold about you, if you believe the information that we hold to be incorrect, you can ask us to update it for you. Should you want us to stop holding your information, then you have the right to ask us to, unless we have reason to keep hold of the information for example, outstanding orders, issues, complaints etc.
To request access/changes to your personal information, please contact us on enquiry@cocklestorm.com
Changes To Our Privacy Policy+
From time to time, this privacy policy may be changed or updated, reflecting how we hold your personal information. Major changes will be highlighted in the policy to allow you to inspect the changes.
This privacy policy was last updated on 24th May 2018
Contact+
To contact us regarding this privacy policy or the personal information held by us, you are able to by:
Email - enquiry@cocklestorm.com
Telephone - 0161 724 9595
In Writing - Cocklestorm Fencing Ltd, Radcliffe Freight Terminal, Bury Road, Radcliffe, M26 2UT
Cocklestorm Fencing Ltd.
Radcliffe Freight Terminal,
Rear of Dulux,
© Copyright 2018 Cocklestorm Fencing Co Ltd, Radcliffe Freight Terminal, Bury Road, Radcliffe, Manchester, M26 2UT
All Rights Reserved | Company No: 1375181 | VAT No: 323 854 360
Tel: 0161 724 9595 Fax: 0161 724 9596 email: enquiry@cocklestorm.com
To top
